Lily McIlroy Russell papers, Inclusive: 1897-1968; Bulk: 1942-1958
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Collected Materials, 1905-1968; 4
  - Henry Lee Graves (3 of 3), undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Henry Lee Graves Correspondence (1 of 3), 1905-1967 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Henry Lee Graves Correspondence (2 of 3), 1905-1967 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Henry Lee Graves Correspondence (3 of 3), 1905-1967 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Red Cross, 1945, undated (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - A.S.I.D. Pictures, undated (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Military Pictures, undated (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - "Baylor Diamond Jubilee", 1921 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Datebook and Memo Book, 1957, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - "God's Minute", 1923 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - "God's Message", 1931 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Datebooks, 1949-1953 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - "The Baylor Monthly" Volume 5, 1929-1930 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - "The Baylor Monthly" Volume 6, 1930-1931 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - "The Exeter Book", 1931 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Holy Bibles (1 of 3), undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Holy Bibles (2 of 3), undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Holy Bibles (3 of 3), undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - "The Greatest Writing in the World", undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Desk Calendar, 1939 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - "The Cactus" XXV, 1918 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Photographs, 1907-1920, undated; 5
  The series contains photographs and tintypes. The photographs are of Russell's family, the Claypool family, and friends. There are two types of tintypes in this series. One group of tintypes is loose and have been removed from their original frames. The group of tintypes are set in decorative frames and plush-box holders. These tintypes were given to Russell by Jack Standard and believed to be Baylor family members.
  Some of the loose tintypes have been damaged by scratches and wear and tear due to age. The tintypes in the decorative frames are in excellent condition. The other photographs in this series are in good condition, with minor creases and tears on the edges of the photographs.
  Photographic print; Tintypes
  - General (1 of 5), undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - General (2 of 5), undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - General (3 of 5), undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - General (4 of 5), undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - General (5 of 5), undated (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Photo Album, undated (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - General, 1910-1918, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - General (1 of 2), 1907-1915, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - General (2 of 2), 1907-1915, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - General (1 of 4), undated (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - General (2 of 4), undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - General (3 of 4), undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - General (4 of 4), undated (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Tintypes (1 of 4), undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Tintypes (2 of 4), undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Tintypes (3 of 4), undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Tintypes (4 of 4), undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - General, 1920, undated (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - General, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)